http://www.santafeopera.org/privacy-policy

CalendarTicketing & OperasThe Marriage of FigaroThe Lord of CriesEugene OneginA Midsummer Night's DreamAngel Blue in ConcertApprentice Showcase ScenesTicketing Info Box Office Info & PoliciesSubscriptions Group SalesAccessibilityGift CertificatesSeat MapYour VisitHealth and SafetyYour Night at the OperaGetting HereOpera DiningEnhance Your VisitFrequently Asked QuestionsDestination Santa FeStayEatPlaySpecial EventsOpera ShopDiscoverYouth Opera Storytellers Summer Camp Youth Nights at the Opera Pueblo Opera ProgramHigh School Mastery Programs Opera Makes SenseCommunity & EventsEvents in the CommunityFamily NightsSweet Potato Kicks the SunTouring ProductionsLearningOpera ToursTalks Santa Fe Opera SeminarsSeminar PresentersActive Learning Through OperaEarly Childhood InitiativeOpera for All VoicesSweet Potato Kicks the SunPodcast: Key ChangeInvitational Commissioned Works JuryVolunteerThe Opera GuildsDonateDonate NowDonor BenefitsIndividual GiftsSpecial EventsOpening Weekend Celebration Opening Night DinnersSponsorshipsBusiness & Corporate GiftsPlanned GiftsName Your SeatWays To Give & FAQsAbout UsOverviewOur MissionCompany HistoryTheatre & Opera RanchRecordings New WorksRepertory & ArchivesNews, Press & MediaPeople & EmploymentBoard LeadershipStaff DirectoryMusic Staff Orchestra EmploymentApprentice OpportunitiesSingers TechniciansFacility RentalsProduction RentalsAdvertising OpportunitiesContact UsSearchLogin(0)
Close Navigation
Share with others
Privacy Policy
The Santa Fe Opera is committed to protecting the confidentiality and integrity of your personally identifiable information or PII.
THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
There are several places on this Web site where the visitor’s personally identifiable information may be provided to The Santa Fe Opera through account registration, order forms, application forms, or survey forms. In filling out these forms you may be asked for contact information (name, address, telephone number, e-mail address), financial information (credit card related) and demographic information (age, gender, education level, income level, etc.).
As with most other Internet sites, our Web servers record the Internet Protocol (IP) address of each visitor. This IP address tells us from which domain (such as aol.com) you are visiting, but not your e-mail address. We use the information to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Web site more effectively and to gather broad demographic information.
When providing this personally identifiable information, you are indicating to us your consent that we use it in accordance with the terms and provisions of this policy. This site utilizes cookies to keep track of the visitor's shopping cart and for other purposes.
WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION
We use contact information to send visitors new information about The Santa Fe Opera and its programs through an opt-in request process. The visitor's contact information may also be used at other times when necessary—for example: contact may be related to an online purchase if warranted. The Santa Fe Opera may on occasion share segments of its mailing list with other non-profit organizations for mutually beneficial programs. We do not rent or sell our mailing list with for-profit entities.
The visitor’s financial information is used to execute purchase and donation transactions. We share this information with credit card and check processing organizations as necessary to complete the transactions. The Santa Fe Opera does not retain the identifying financial account information once a transaction is completed.
HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
We are committed to the highest standard of stewardship. Written Company policy makes it the obligation of each Santa Fe Opera employee to protect the confidentiality of our patron information. The Opera takes substantial precautions in seeking to ensure that our systems are secure and that they meet industry standards, including the application of firewalls. When appropriate, we employ user authentication systems, encryption technologies and access control mechanisms.
This site contains links to other Web sites. The Santa Fe Opera is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites.
OPT-IN
Our site provides visitors with the opportunity to request future communications through e-mail and/or the United States postal service.
UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION
We offer the following options for updating information in our database:
Email: patronrecords@santafeopera.org
Call: 505-986-5955
Mail:
Attn: Patron Records Services
The Santa Fe Opera
P.O. Box 2408
Santa Fe, New Mexico 87504-2408
Please include any information that would help us identify you in our database, such as complete contact information (name, postal address and email address) and/or your Santa Fe Opera account number if known.
CONTACTING THE WEB SITE
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Web site, you may contact the box office.
THIRD PARTY USE OF HYPER-LINKS INFORMATION AND OTHER SERVICES
The Santa Fe Opera Web site contains links to other Internet Web sites, including co-branded or other affiliated sites. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other web sites accessed by a link from The Santa Fe Opera website, including such sites' use of any information and use of any marks.
You may be able to access certain information related to third parties at the site, or via links or clicks from the site, regarding the goods or services of third parties. You understand and agree that your access to or use of those services is a matter entirely between you and the third parties. The Santa Fe Opera shall have no liability whatsoever for any such access or use of information or purchased products or services of Web site visitor’s interaction with any and all third parties.
SECURITY
We have attempted and will continue to attempt to establish procedures to ensure that your information is both accurate and safe from unauthorized access. Nevertheless, you understand and agree that "perfect" security does not exist anywhere, including on the Internet. Information you send to this site, including e-mail messages, will not be encrypted unless we advise you that it will be encrypted. Our Web site is protected by a firewall and monitored for security.
Buy Tickets
800-280-4654
